Business Central is rapidly expanding,
attracting larger and more complex
organizations.
And rapidly expanding with Microsoft
Cloud
Annoying, right? When something that
should just work suddenly stops working
on it, especially when you're in the
middle of something important. Let's try
that again.
We continuously evolve every layer of
our cloud platform and tooling based on
the real-world signals from our
ecosystem to stay ahead of that demand.
And this is where you come in.
Me? No, not you. You. Your products
already enable countless industries for
Business Central customers. Unhandled
performance bottlenecks can ripple
across this otherwise magnificent system
and impact the overall experience for
our users.
High performance isn't a destination.
It's a continuous journey. The teams
that win are the ones that keep people
refining and modernizing and challenging
their code and their practices.
Those that take performance seriously
can now leverage the optimal performance
initiative, building the skills, the
tool, and the engineering discipline,
including agent capabilities, to manage
performance proactively, not reactively.
As optimal performance helped us to
improve performance by making
performance a top priority in our daily
business.
>> It's a shared responsibility to make the
platform run as fast as possible. It
makes everything better. It made me more
enthusiastic about using LLMs in coding
than everybody in total in the last few
years. It's much more automated. We
improved the performance by 20%.
>> More than 40%. 2.5 times faster than
95%.
>> A 93% improvement overall. I thought we
could improve it a bit, but I didn't
thought we could go that far. There's
definitely no reason why a partner
shouldn't join. It's an excellent
opportunity to upskill the team. We're
are the future with it. It should be an
operator. You've heard it, Optimal
raises the bar. Faster, more predictable
systems that scale, happier customers,
lower support costs, and more capacity
for you to grow and differentiate.
To put it simply, modern platforms
demand modern code, and we are here to
help you to stand top of that game.
Come and learn more about the Optimal
Performance Initiative. We're very keen
to be working with you.